[{"answer": "How far does this train go", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm going to that place, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Perhaps I don't take it so lightly", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Is it? I expected to go to the that place Royal. Should I have a reservation", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Indefinitely", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " You don't know", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I've always been a heel. I guess I always will be", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "It's the only pose I have left. I'm sunk. Broke. I don't even have my hotel bill", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Mr. my friend", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Rather more than a little something, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Would it make you anymore amusing", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I didn't say anything", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What'll you have, my friend", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " You, my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "It's quite unimportant, Mr. my friend. After all, you got what you wanted", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I have no intension of being nasty, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "There isn't one.. That anyone would believe. I went for a walk after dinner, down to the ocean...alone... I came up and went to bed. I didn't sleep very well. Then there was a thunderstorm. And it began to rain. I went across to close the French door. That's the first time I saw him out there", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Not with my consent, strange as it seems. I don't know how he got in. I don't know anything", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "They'll know whether he killed himself", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "How did you meet him", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "He knew the immigration officer. He eased himself in", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "That's all there is", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " What are you doing here", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What do you want", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " That's not enough", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "He saw my face too", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "With what motive", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "He was very easy to hate. If you'll look in your mirror, when you are in a better tempe", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "All right, let's see the buzzer", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "So you're not a cop", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Anything I can do about it", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Good morning, Mr. my friend", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Mr. my friend would like you to call him", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "A thousand", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Got the information on you", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " Got it on you", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Get it in half an hour", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "We wouldn't have met at all", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You were a galahad, compared to some cops I've known", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You were a galahad, compared to some cops I've known", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Who hasn'", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Is it a crime", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You were there when I last saw him", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You understand perfectly", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "There isn't anything you can do", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "One of those nice long manila envelope", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "You get it's brother", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "That's my hard luc", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "They call me my friend", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "What are you going to d", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "What proper grounds?  You can't be in love with me.  You hardly know me.  I'm not in love with you", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I don't know, sir", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Nobody's covering her, I detached the officer assigned to that duty", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Don't kid me.  You don't think she murdered my friend", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "That COULD BE TOLD", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "It could have been an accident", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Not if she knew she wouldn't be believed", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I don't know why.  As a matter of fact, I don't know anything", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I agree with you perfectly.  But when did time ever help a fool", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "They're going to arrest me", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " I have my own warrant.  Stop a minute, please", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "We got a lot of it out here", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "No doubt.  We have something he may not have counted on", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": " Mine", "docId": "playback.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "my friend was dead enough", "qsentId": 66}]